<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on OpenEL Association</title><link>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on OpenEL Association</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:31:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What's Ahead for the OpenELA?</title><link>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/the-road-ahead/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:31:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/the-road-ahead/</guid><description>In the final blog and video of this 3-part introduction to OpenELA, we have Alan Clark, member of the office of the CTO at SUSE. Alan details the early foundation that was laid when OpenELA began in 2023 and goes on to talk about the planned projects for 2024 and beyond. A summary of the discussion is offered below the video.
OpenELA’s primary focus in 2024 and beyond is to ensure the long term future of this open, compatible enterprise standard.</description></item><item><title>Why the OpenELA was created</title><link>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/why-was-openela-created/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:18:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/why-was-openela-created/</guid><description>In the first blog post of this series, we shared Gregory Kurtzer’s introduction to OpenELA. He talked about the collaboration among CIQ, SUSE, and Oracle in forming the nonprofit as a commitment to building an open source base that brings longevity and stability to the entire enterprise Linux ecosystem.
In this second blog post and video, we hear from Wim Coekaerts, Executive Vice President of software development at Oracle. He shares why OpenELA was created to be a community-driven standard in the enterprise Linux ecosystem and how it ensures a stable and resilient future for both upstream and downstream communities to leverage enterprise Linux.</description></item><item><title>Meet OpenELA - the What, the Why, and the Plan for the future</title><link>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/meet-openela-what-why-future/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:43:32 -0400</pubDate><guid>$%7BPREVIEW_BASE_URL%7D/preview_aa8b050a2e0e937a82f6d463c1dfa71a010b4955/blog/meet-openela-what-why-future/</guid><description>It’s like the new neighbors who just moved in down the block; you see them in the yard and wave as you pass by, but it’s nice to sit down and finally get to know them. That’s what the founding organizations of OpenELA are doing with this 3-part blog and video series—a meet and greet, if you will. We wanted to offer a personal introduction to OpenELA, sharing why the organization was started, what it’s here to do, and what exciting advancements lie ahead.</description></item></channel></rss>